Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Memorabilia 6169 MB
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Memorabilia
1999- 2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees (NUHHCE)
Local 1199 Drug amd Hospital Union
6169 MB
0.67 cubic feet
0.7 linear ft.
Memorabilia.
8430165
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 15, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 24, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6085 G: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project "Frederick Douglass and His Time" Posters 6084 G: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Women of Hope Poster Sets 6089 G: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Posters 6069: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Additional Files 6140 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio Recordings 6140: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project 5929: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Records 6169: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Files 6169 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio-Visual Materials 6169 P: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Photographs 5929 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio-Visual Materials 5929 MB: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Memorabilia 5929 P: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Photographs
National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees; National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees. Local 1199 Drug & Hospital Union (New York, N.Y.); Bread and Roses Cultural Project
8430165
- T.V. Theme - children - sheet music (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 1199 Sheet music (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 1199 more sheet music (Box 1, Folder 3)
- sheet music (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Different poster - Theater in the hospital (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 1199 Paper Hat (Box 1, Folder 6)
- SEIU Greenhouse Cultural Program Calendars (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 1199 SEIU News - June 2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Unseen America NYS: pictures of working lives taken by working hands (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Scope and Contents
  2 copies
- 3 SEIU - Women of Hope Calendars (1999) (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Coretta Scott King: A Message to Hospital and Nursing Home Workers (Box 1, Folder 11)
  33-1/3 RPM
- Take Care: A Musical Revue of Life in the Hospitals - (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Presented by District 1199's Bread and Roses Project; (1 phonograph album, album cover and 2 info sheets)
- The Union Democracy Built - (Box 1, Folder 13)
  1 phonograph album and cover